I am going to now show you about the stroller and some key components to it so that if you were to buy one, you would get the most for your money and for your intentions.
This is a jogging stroller because it's has three wheels and the wheels are large and for altering activities such as the sand, dirt paths but also the cement.
They have newer ones that have a swivel front wheel which is nice when you are taking the stroller maybe to the mall or shopping or to the grocery store but most of them the wheel is straight and you will want to have it be locked in if you were running with the stroller.
This stroller is great for the beach because the wheels are plastic instead of metal spoke and so you don't have to worry about them getting rested because if you are spending money on a stroller, you want it to last not just for one kid but probably at least two kids.
This specific stroller runs about two hundred and fifty to three hundred dollars and if you want to buy a jogging stroller, I would plan to spend at least a hundred and fifty.
Two other components that are important on the jogging stroller is the sun shade so that your little one is covered from the elements.
Some of these have very small sun shades and in that case you end up clipping a blanket to the top of it which is difficult because sometimes that falls off and then if you cover it completely with the blanket then the baby can't see all the wonderful places you're taking them.
The sun shade is great.
Also, for when it is the sun is not in their face it can fold up all the way.
Lastly, base on your height and your spouse's height, you want to make sure you buy a stroller that fits your body and so you want to have the handle that hits around bright your waist.
If something too high, it going to put pressure on your shoulders and it's going to make you really tight.
If it's something to low, you're going to have lower back pain and if you're planning to use this a few times a week for one to three miles, so you would want it to fit your body.